https://www.guestline.com/privacy-policy-guestline/

Close
Search Who we work withIndependent HotelsHotel GroupsPub CompaniesManagement CompaniesServiced ApartmentsBest WesternThe Guest Experience PlatformCloud Technology in HotelsContact-free Hotel ExperienceOverviewDirect Booking ManagerGuestStay – Digital RegistrationPayLinkProperty ManagementOverviewProperty Management SystemGuestPayCentral ReservationsC&BEPoSDistributionOverviewChannel ManagementGuest EngagementOverviewWebsuiteDirect Booking ManagerRevSpaMaking great solutions even betterOur Integration PartnersBecome Guestline PMS Integration PartnerEverything you need to knowOur peopleCareersGlobal officesServicesWith you every step of the wayTraining and implementationSupportSecurity and ComplianceContact UsWhat have we been up to?NewsBlogEvents & ExhibitionsSuccess StoriesPrivacy PolicyGuestline Privacy Policy - the Guestline company 2018The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.We are resolutely committed to protecting, safeguarding and respecting your privacy.We will only hold, process and transfer the data that we collect about you and which personally identifies you in accordance with applicable laws, this Privacy Policy, GDPR and any terms set out at the point(s) at which data is collected by the Guestline company (“Collection Terms”).  If there is any inconsistency between the Collection Terms and this Privacy Policy, the Collection Terms will prevail.Except where stated or the context requires otherwise, references in this Privacy Policy to “you”, “your” or “yours” are to be taken as references to the site user and, where applicable, the user’s company and references to “us” or “we” are to be taken as references to the Guestline company.What personal data do we collect?We only collect personal data about you for business to business reasons:Information you provide when you use the “contact us” facility or fill in any enquiry or other forms on the site (for example, your name, email address and telephone number);If you contact us by phone or support email address, we may keep a record of that and any subsequent business correspondence.Please ensure you always provide accurate data and you agree to update it as necessary in the manner specified below.  You also agree that, in the absence of any update, we can assume that the data you have provided is correct.How we use personal dataBy contacting us or requesting a contact you hereby explicitly consent to your personal data being collected/received by us and processed by us as required in order to:contact you and provide you with information or services that you have requested and deal with any matters arising as a result of that contact; and/orenable a member of the Guestline company to contact you and provide you with information or services that you have requested and deal with any matters arising as a result of that contact.Disclosure of personal data to third partiesBy requesting contact from the Guestline company you hereby explicitly consent to your personal data being transferred and/or disclosed (whether inside or outside the European Economic Area) to and/or processed by:members of Guestline company for the purposes set out in the section above headed ‘How We Use Personal Data’;data storage providers used in the operation of the site and/or the provision of any of the services provided through it (these providers, for example Microsoft  Azure cloud services, do not have direct access to the personal data unless specified otherwise on the site);a future purchaser of some or all of our assets or, where applicable, the assets of all or part of Guestline company; andin the unlikely event that we believe in good faith that we are required to do so: (a) by court order or other legal/regulatory requirement; or (b) in order to protect our rights/property or those of our clients and/or their employees.GeneralYour Right(s) of access, deleting, deactivating and amending your personal data:Subject to the provisions of applicable law and GDPR you may obtain copy(ies) of the personal data (if any) we hold about you by contacting us via the site’s “contact us” facility.Additionally, if you wish to delete, deactivate or amend the personal data, or find out what personal data (if any) we are holding about you, please contact us via the site’s “contact us” facility.Retention of personal data:We are only allowed to retain your personal data for so long as is necessary having regard to the purpose of the processing.  We may therefore delete personal data after an appropriate period.Changes to our Privacy Policy:We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice and will post the updated Privacy Policy on the site so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Please ensure that you read this Privacy Policy regularly. Your continued use of the site following any changes will constitute acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.Newsletter SignupUse the form below to signup to our mailing list - you can then choose how you'd like to be contacted: Close
CloseSupport EnquiriesContact NameProperty / Group Name*Telephone No.*Country*Email* Enquiry*
By ticking this box you agree to receiving further information and news from us on new products, services or events. More information can be found in our privacy policy.PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged. Submit
We use cookies to give you the best experience possible. Click 'Accept' to Continue exploring. If you wish to opt-out then you can click the 'Reject' button. Read More Accept Reject Privacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary Always Enabled
